{
    "subject": "resource/William_Petty",
    "predicate": "ontology/era",
    "object": "resource/17th-century_philosophy",
    "human_readable": "William Petty was active in the 17th-century philosophy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9790036082267761,
            "question": "During what century was William Petty active in philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6694165468215942,
            "question": "How did William Petty's work influence later philosophers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.613300085067749,
            "question": "What were some major philosophical ideas explored in the 17th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6085072159767151,
            "question": "What is considered to be William Petty's most important contribution to philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6030296087265015,
            "question": "Can you name some prominent philosophers from the 17th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5855691432952881,
            "question": "What area of study was William Petty involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5188674330711365,
            "question": "What were some key challenges or debates faced by philosophers in the 17th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46959009766578674,
            "question": "Were there any significant movements or schools of thought in 17th-century philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3525710701942444,
            "question": "How did the social and political context of the 17th century shape philosophical thought?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3217918872833252,
            "question": "Did William Petty write any influential books or treatises?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=William Petty was active in the 17th-century philosophy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7760_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the social and political context of the 17th century shape philosophical thought?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7760_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant movements or schools of thought in 17th-century philosophy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7760_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some key challenges or debates faced by philosophers in the 17th century?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7760_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7760_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sir William Petty's activities and contributions during the 17th century, including his work with the Royal Society, his involvement in surveying Ireland, and his writings on various subjects. This supports the statement that William Petty was active in 17th-century philosophy, given his intellectual pursuits and scientific contributions of that era."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}